[

    {
        "question": "1*3 = ?",
        "answers": [ "1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13", "14", "15", "16", "17", "18", "19", "20" ],
        "correctAnswer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "2*3 = ?",
        "answers": [ "1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13", "14", "15", "16", "17", "18", "19", "20" ],
        "correctAnswer": "6"
    },    {
        "question": "3*3 = ?",
        "answers": [ "1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13", "14", "15", "16", "17", "18", "19", "20" ],
        "correctAnswer": "9"
    },    {
        "question": "4*3 = ?",
        "answers": [ "1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13", "14", "15", "16", "17", "18", "19", "20" ],
        "correctAnswer": "12"
    },    {
        "question": "5*3 = ?",
        "answers": [ "1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13", "14", "15", "16", "17", "18", "19", "20" ],
        "correctAnswer": "15"
    },    {
        "question": "6*3 = ?",
        "answers": [ "18" ],
        "correctAnswer": "18"
    },    {
        "question": "7*3 = ?",
        "answers": [ "21" ],
        "correctAnswer": "21"
    },    {
        "question": "8*3 = ?",
        "answers": [ "24" ],
        "correctAnswer": "24"
    },    {
        "question": "9*3 = ?",
        "answers": [ "27" ],
        "correctAnswer": "27"
    },    
    {
        "question": "10*3 = ?",
        "answers": [ "3","30", "40", "60", "13", "15", "20", "300", "33" ],
        "correctAnswer": "30"
    },   
     {
        "question": "1*2 = ?",
        "answers": [ "1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13", "14", "15", "16", "17", "18", "19", "20" ],
        "correctAnswer": "2"
    },    {
        "question": "2*2 = ?",
        "answers": [ "1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13", "14", "15", "16", "17", "18", "19", "20" ],
        "correctAnswer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "3*2 = ?",
        "answers": [ "1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13", "14", "15", "16", "17", "18", "19", "20" ],
        "correctAnswer": "6"
    },  
    {
        "question": "4*2 = ?",
        "answers": [ "1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13", "14", "15", "16", "17", "18", "19", "20" ],
        "correctAnswer": "8"
    },  
    {
        "question": "5*2 = ?",
        "answers": [ "1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13", "14", "15", "16", "17", "18", "19", "20" ],
        "correctAnswer": "10"
    },  
    {
        "question": "2*6 = ?",
        "answers": [ "1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13", "14", "15", "16", "17", "18", "19", "20" ],
        "correctAnswer": "12"
    },  
    {
        "question": "7*2 = ?",
        "answers": [ "1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13", "14", "15", "16", "17", "18", "19", "20" ],
        "correctAnswer": "14"
    },  
    {
        "question": "8*2 = ?",
        "answers": [ "1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13", "14", "15", "16", "17", "18", "19", "20" ],
        "correctAnswer": "16"
    },  
    {
        "question": "9*2 = ?",
        "answers": [ "1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13", "14", "15", "16", "17", "18", "19", "20" ],
        "correctAnswer": "18"
    },  
    {
        "question": "10*2 = ?",
        "answers": [ "1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10", "11", "12", "13", "14", "15", "16", "17", "18", "19", "20" ],
        "correctAnswer": "20"
    },

    {
        "question": "10*4 = ?",
        "answers": [ "3","30", "40", "60", "13", "15", "10", "80" ],
        "correctAnswer": "40"
    },   
    {
        "question": "10*5 = ?",
        "answers": [ "50" ],
        "correctAnswer": "50"
    }

]